Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The wind once paused by the rain streaked window♪
♪توقفت الرياح ذات مرة عند النافذة التي لطختها قطرات المطر♪
♪Sketching you in gentle strokes♪
♪أرسمك بخطوط رقيقة♪
♪From the old town, cooking smoke curled upward♪
♪من البلدة القديمة، تصاعد دخان الطهي♪
♪Smoothing the tide of my restless thoughts♪
♪تهدئة موجة أفكاري المضطربة♪
=A Vow in the Dark=
=عهد في الظلام=
Jie Chuan.
جي تشوان.
=Episode 15=
=الحلقة 15=
I will never forget you.
لن أنساك أبداً.
Ji Li...
جي لي ...
Ji Li!
جي لي!
I only have you in my heart,
أنت وحدك في قلبي،
only you.
أنت فقط.
You were in my illusion,
كنتَ في وهمي،
connected with my soul,
متصلة بروحي،
and shared my emotions.
وشاركت مشاعري.
As long as I exist,
ما دمت موجوداً،
you will not perish.
لن تهلك.
With my reverse scale,
بمقياسي العكسي،
you will be alright.
ستكون بخير.
Ji Li, Ji Li!
جي لي، جي لي!
I saw her star dim
رأيت نجمها يخفت
in Flowing Star;
في النجمة المتدفقة؛
I came to save her.
جئت لإنقاذها.
Without immortal bones, she cannot live.
بدون عظام خالدة، لا تستطيع أن تعيش.
Yet
حتى الآن
there is one chance left.
لم يتبق سوى فرصة واحدة.
Bones can be re-forged,
يمكن إعادة تشكيل العظام،
and broken shards re-grown.
وتنمو الشظايا المكسورة من جديد.
In the Abyss of Wasteland
في هاوية الأرض القاحلة
blooms the Rejoining Flower,
تتفتح زهرة الالتحام،
but it opens only
لكنها تفتح فقط
when fed with blood of an ancient divine beast.
عندما تتغذى على دم وحش إلهي قديم.
The Candle Dragon will work.
سينجح تنين الشمعة.
Yet you must pass through the Grave Gorge.
ومع ذلك، يجب عليك المرور عبر وادي غريف.
In recent years,
في السنوات الأخيرة،
no one has entered and lived.
لم يدخل أحد ويعيش.
The Grave Gorge...
مضيق غريف...
What is so hard about that?
ما الصعب في ذلك؟
(Wasteland, Grave Gorge)
(أرض قاحلة، وادي المقابر)
♪Thin wisps of smoke weave through the river♪
♪خيوط رقيقة من الدخان تتسلل عبر النهر♪
♪Melodies and wine fade, drunk beneath the sunset♪
تتلاشى الألحان والنبيذ، ونحن نُشرب تحت غروب الشمس.
♪Lonely light and sword shadow sway the falling leaves♪
♪ضوء وحيد وظل سيف يتمايلان مع الأوراق المتساقطة♪
♪Laughing at my recklessness in this life♪
أضحك على تهوّري في هذه الحياة
♪You come to me in every way♪
♪تأتون إليّ بكل الطرق♪
♪Filling my dreams with tangled love and hate♪
♪أملأ أحلامي بمزيج من الحب والكراهية♪
♪All my best years were for you♪
♪كل أجمل سنوات عمري كانت من أجلك♪
♪At the far edge of the world where lanterns fade♪
♪على الحافة البعيدة للعالم حيث تخبو الفوانيس♪
♪Through the mortal dust, time flows with its trials♪
♪عبر غبار الفناء، يتدفق الزمن بمحنه♪
♪Joys and sorrows ease grief♪
♪الأفراح والأحزان تخفف من وطأة الحزن♪
♪At dusk, petals fall as winter snow carries the starlight♪
♪عند الغسق، تتساقط البتلات بينما يحمل ثلج الشتاء ضوء النجوم♪
You aren't as wicked
أنت لست شريراً إلى هذا الحد
as the tales claim.
كما تزعم الحكايات.
♪Love fades easily, yet is hard to forget♪
♪الحب يزول بسهولة، لكن من الصعب نسيانه♪
♪You come to me in every way♪
♪تأتون إليّ بكل الطرق♪
♪Filling my dreams with tangled love and hate♪
♪أملأ أحلامي بمزيج من الحب والكراهية♪
To grow spirit plants,
لزراعة النباتات الروحية،
I need Taiqing Power.
أحتاج إلى قوة تاي تشينغ.
♪All my best years were for you♪
♪كل أجمل سنوات عمري كانت من أجلك♪
♪At the far edge of the world♪
♪على أقصى حافة العالم♪
As expected of the Demon Sovereign,
كما هو متوقع من سيد الشياطين،
you're so handsome and kind.
أنت وسيم ولطيف للغاية.
♪Through the mortal dust, time flows with its trials♪
♪عبر غبار الفناء، يتدفق الزمن بمحنه♪
Jie Chuan,
جي تشوان,
have you forgotten I'm just a goldfish?
هل نسيت أنني مجرد سمكة ذهبية؟
♪At dusk, petals fall as winter snow carries the starlight♪
♪عند الغسق، تتساقط البتلات بينما يحمل ثلج الشتاء ضوء النجوم♪
♪Across endless lifetimes, the ballad endures♪
♪عبر أجيال لا حصر لها، تبقى الأغنية خالدة♪
♪Through the mortal dust, time flows with its trials♪
♪عبر غبار الفناء، يتدفق الزمن بمحنه♪
♪Joys and sorrows ease grief♪
♪الأفراح والأحزان تخفف من وطأة الحزن♪
♪At dusk, petals fall as winter snow carries the starlight♪
♪عند الغسق، تتساقط البتلات بينما يحمل ثلج الشتاء ضوء النجوم♪
♪Across endless lifetimes, the ballad endures♪
♪عبر أجيال لا حصر لها، تبقى الأغنية خالدة♪
♪Love fades easily, yet is hard to forget♪
♪الحب يزول بسهولة، لكن من الصعب نسيانه♪
Watch out! He's going to detonate his soul!
احذروا! إنه على وشك أن يفجر روحه!
What else?
ماذا بعد؟
No more calling me stupid,
لا مزيد من وصفي بالغباء،
no more locking me,
لا مزيد من حبسي،
and no more striking my master!
ولن أضرب سيدي بعد الآن!
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
I'll follow you every lead.
سأتبع كل خيط ترشدني إليه.
Ji Li,
جي لي,
are you unwilling to wake up?
ألا ترغب في الاستيقاظ؟
Sorry, I should never have left you.
آسف، ما كان ينبغي لي أن أتركك.
Ji Li,
جي لي,
Jie Chuan
جي تشوان
loves you.
يحبك.
Ji Li...
جي لي ...
Ji Li!
جي لي!
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Where is Ji Li?
أين جي لي؟
How is she?
كيف حالها؟
She woke long ago.
لقد استيقظت منذ زمن طويل.
Then where is she?
إذن أين هي؟
Oh, no.
أوه، لا.
It's my loose tongue;
هذا بسبب لساني المتهور؛
I mentioned the Grave Gorge.
لقد ذكرتُ مضيق غريف.
She must have gone there.
لا بد أنها ذهبت إلى هناك.
Grave Gorge...
مضيق غريف...
Ji Li!
جي لي!
You're hurt.
أنت مصاب.
Just a scratch;
مجرد خدش؛
don't worry about me.
لا تقلق عليّ.
I brought you water from Flowing Star.
أحضرت لك الماء من النجم المتدفق.
Drink a little.
اشرب قليلاً.
Right now, the immortals
في الوقت الحالي، الخالدون
hates the demons to the bone.
يكره الشياطين حتى النخاع.
Plus, Jie Chuan broke his promise.
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، أخلّ جي تشوان بوعده.
If they know about your two,
إذا كانوا يعلمون بأمركما،
exile will be the least of your troubles.
سيكون النفي أهون مشاكلك.
That was only a misunderstanding.
كان ذلك مجرد سوء فهم.
I must return and explain to Master;
يجب أن أعود وأشرح الأمر للسيد؛
perhaps
ربما
I can lessen the immortals' bias against Jie Chuan.
بإمكاني أن أخفف من تحيز الخالدين ضد جي تشوان.
You're in trouble yourself;
أنت نفسك في ورطة؛
why fret over him?
لماذا القلق بشأنه؟
You should just go to the Demon Realm
يجب عليك الذهاب إلى عالم الشياطين
and spare yourself this lovesick pain.
وتجنب هذا الألم العاطفي.
The great war began because of me;
بدأت الحرب العظمى بسببي؛
I have to return.
يجب أن أعود.
Yet I can't stop worrying about him.
لكنني لا أستطيع التوقف عن القلق بشأنه.
He suffered these wounds
لقد أصيب بهذه الجروح
for my sake.
من أجلي.
(Ji Li)
(جي لي)
(wants to return?)
(هل يريد العودة؟)
(No. She must not leave.)
(لا. يجب ألا تغادر.)
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Your wounds...
جروحك...
Wait.
انتظر.
Your power hasn't recovered.
لم تستعد قوتك بعد.
Let me check his injuries first;
دعني أتحقق من إصاباته أولاً؛
then we'll think of a plan.
ثم سنفكر في خطة.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
How can this be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا؟
Cultivation backlash for a Demon Sovereign?
هل ستكون هناك ردة فعل عكسية تجاه سيد شيطاني؟
What do we do?
ماذا نفعل؟
I'll try again.
سأحاول مرة أخرى.
Ji Li, things are tricky now.
جي لي، الأمور معقدة الآن.
Why don't you stay here?
لماذا لا تبقى هنا؟
I'll fetch
سأحضر
Hong Zhua to treat him.
هونغ تشوا سيعالجه.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
You won't see him for a while.
لن تراه لفترة من الوقت.
I'll go.
سأذهب.
Jie Chuan, hold on.
جي تشوان، انتظر.
Am I that fragile?
هل أنا هشٌّ إلى هذه الدرجة؟
I'll circulate for a while.
سأبقى أتجول لفترة من الوقت.
I feel lively; I'm fine.
أشعر بالحيوية؛ أنا بخير.
You two are just happy
أنتما سعيدان للغاية
to endure each other.
أن يتحمل كل منهما الآخر.
All right, I won't disturb you.
حسناً، لن أزعجك.
As for what you asked,
أما بخصوص سؤالك،
I'll pass the word to Hong Zhua.
سأبلغ هونغ تشوا بالأمر.
As for his illness,
أما بالنسبة لمرضه،
as long as you stay,
طالما بقيتَ،
he needs no the drug at all.
هو ليس بحاجة إلى الدواء على الإطلاق.
♪Thin wisps of smoke weave through the river♪
♪خيوط رقيقة من الدخان تتسلل عبر النهر♪
♪Melodies and wine fade, drunk beneath the sunset♪
تتلاشى الألحان والنبيذ، ونحن نُشرب تحت غروب الشمس.
♪Lonely light and sword shadow sway the falling leaves♪
♪ضوء وحيد وظل سيف يتمايلان مع الأوراق المتساقطة♪
♪Laughing at my recklessness in this life♪
أضحك على تهوّري في هذه الحياة
♪You come to me in every way♪
♪تأتون إليّ بكل الطرق♪
♪Filling my dreams with tangled love and hate♪
♪أملأ أحلامي بمزيج من الحب والكراهية♪
♪All my best years were for you♪
♪كل أجمل سنوات عمري كانت من أجلك♪
♪At the far edge of the world where lanterns fade♪
♪على الحافة البعيدة للعالم حيث تخبو الفوانيس♪
♪Through the mortal dust, time flows with its trials♪
♪عبر غبار الفناء، يتدفق الزمن بمحنه♪
♪Joys and sorrows ease grief♪
♪الأفراح والأحزان تخفف من وطأة الحزن♪
♪At dusk, petals fall as winter snow carries the starlight♪
♪عند الغسق، تتساقط البتلات بينما يحمل ثلج الشتاء ضوء النجوم♪
♪Across endless lifetimes, the ballad endures♪
♪عبر أجيال لا حصر لها، تبقى الأغنية خالدة♪